{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Water Dock Repair Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40440/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40440,"taskName":"Water Dock - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair a Dock","xmTaskDescriptor":"Water Dock Repair Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1704,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Water Dock waterfront","textMessagingName":"Repr Water Dock","rolloverLongDesc":"Usually involves pounding or boring underwater. May involve wood, concrete, plastic \u0026 composite building materials. Includes boat houses, ramps, swimming platforms, berths, boat cranes \u0026 all other waterfront installations.","rolloverShortDesc":"Repair waterfront structures.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair a Dock.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Dock Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix a Water or Boat Dock","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":21,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Water Dock Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Water Dock - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Water Dock Project","urlName":"Water-Dock-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Dock Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Water, Dock, waterfront","emcCategoryOid":-12023,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":731,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40440/":{"taskOID":40440,"originalTaskOID":40440,"setID":731,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4812,"questionDisplayText":"Service Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs servicing? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1022,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bent frame","answerDisplayText":"Bent frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5025,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Raising and lowering mechanism doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Raising and lowering mechanism doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4119,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Needs to be secured","answerDisplayText":"Needs to be secured","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7077,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood has dry rot","answerDisplayText":"Wood has dry rot","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1691,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cracked concrete","answerDisplayText":"Cracked concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6208,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Surface is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Surface is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4060,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Need new floats","answerDisplayText":"Need new floats","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4065,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Need new tires","answerDisplayText":"Need new tires","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2295,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Expansion needed","answerDisplayText":"Expansion needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5067,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Reconfiguration needed","answerDisplayText":"Reconfiguration needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4432,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Options needed","answerDisplayText":"Options needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4809,"questionDisplayText":"Dock Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of dock is it? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4647,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Permanent","answerDisplayText":"Permanent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4809,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Portable","answerDisplayText":"Portable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6053,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Standing","answerDisplayText":"Standing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2525,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Floating","answerDisplayText":"Floating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6214,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Suspended","answerDisplayText":"Suspended","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4812,"questionDisplayText":"Service Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs servicing? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1022,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bent frame","answerDisplayText":"Bent frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5025,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Raising and lowering mechanism doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Raising and lowering mechanism doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4119,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Needs to be secured","answerDisplayText":"Needs to be secured","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7077,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood has dry rot","answerDisplayText":"Wood has dry rot","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1691,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cracked concrete","answerDisplayText":"Cracked concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6208,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Surface is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Surface is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4060,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Need new floats","answerDisplayText":"Need new floats","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4065,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Need new tires","answerDisplayText":"Need new tires","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2295,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Expansion needed","answerDisplayText":"Expansion needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5067,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Reconfiguration needed","answerDisplayText":"Reconfiguration needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4432,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Options needed","answerDisplayText":"Options needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1022,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Bent frame","answerDisplayText":"Bent frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5025,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Raising and lowering mechanism doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Raising and lowering mechanism doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4119,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Needs to be secured","answerDisplayText":"Needs to be secured","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7077,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood has dry rot","answerDisplayText":"Wood has dry rot","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1691,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Cracked concrete","answerDisplayText":"Cracked concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6208,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Surface is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Surface is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4060,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Need new floats","answerDisplayText":"Need new floats","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4065,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Need new tires","answerDisplayText":"Need new tires","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2295,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Expansion needed","answerDisplayText":"Expansion needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5067,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Reconfiguration needed","answerDisplayText":"Reconfiguration needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4432,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Options needed","answerDisplayText":"Options needed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4809,"questionDisplayText":"Dock Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of dock is it? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4647,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Permanent","answerDisplayText":"Permanent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4809,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Portable","answerDisplayText":"Portable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6053,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Standing","answerDisplayText":"Standing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2525,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Floating","answerDisplayText":"Floating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6214,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Suspended","answerDisplayText":"Suspended","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4647,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Permanent","answerDisplayText":"Permanent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4809,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Portable","answerDisplayText":"Portable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6053,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Standing","answerDisplayText":"Standing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2525,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Floating","answerDisplayText":"Floating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6214,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Suspended","answerDisplayText":"Suspended","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}